{
    "subject": "resource/Damn_Seagulls",
    "predicate": "property/origin",
    "object": "Helsinki, Finland",
    "human_readable": "Damn Seagulls originated in Helsinki, Finland.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9346418976783752,
            "question": "Has Damn Seagulls performed outside of Finland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9100885987281799,
            "question": "Where did Damn Seagulls originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.508965253829956,
            "question": "What type of group is Damn Seagulls?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4942067563533783,
            "question": "What country is Helsinki in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39718884229660034,
            "question": "Are there any other musical groups that originated in Helsinki?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2644749879837036,
            "question": "Is Helsinki the capital of Finland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1949426829814911,
            "question": "Besides music, what other things are Helsinki known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19244198501110077,
            "question": "What kind of music does Damn Seagulls play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09503040462732315,
            "question": "What is the name of Helsinki's main airport?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08370832353830338,
            "question": "Can you name a famous band or musical artist from Helsinki?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Damn Seagulls originated in Helsinki, Finland.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2173_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Helsinki's main airport?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2173_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of music does Damn Seagulls play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2173_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides music, what other things are Helsinki known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2173_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2173_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2173_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2173_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2173_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2173_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2173_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2173_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2173_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2173_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2173_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents contain information about the Finnish rock group Damn Seagulls, and all of them mention that they originated in Helsinki, Finland. Therefore, the triple \"Damn Seagulls originated in Helsinki, Finland\" is supported by the context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents repeatedly mention that Damn Seagulls are a band from Helsinki, Finland. Therefore, the statement \"Damn Seagulls originated in Helsinki, Finland\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}